<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://www.codebreakers.uk/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://www.codebreakers.uk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-04-27T07:16:28-05:00</updated><id>https://www.codebreakers.uk/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Codebreakers</title><subtitle>The main website for the codebreakers project</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Vultr ADT Tutorials</title><link href="https://www.codebreakers.uk/adtvultrtutorials/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Vultr ADT Tutorials" /><published>2021-11-01T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-11-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://www.codebreakers.uk/tutorials</id><author><name></name></author><category term="agiledeploymenttoolkit" /><summary type="html">There’s a few options here for learning how to use this toolkit with the Vultr cloudhost.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Introduction</title><link href="https://www.codebreakers.uk/introduction/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Introduction" /><published>2021-11-01T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-11-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://www.codebreakers.uk/adt-introduction</id><author><name></name></author><category term="agiledeploymenttoolkit" /><summary type="html">Agile Deployment Toolkit</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Agile Deployment Toolkit Tech Overview</title><link href="https://www.codebreakers.uk/agiledeploymenttoolkittechoverview/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Agile Deployment Toolkit Tech Overview" /><published>2021-11-01T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-11-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://www.codebreakers.uk/adt-techoverview</id><author><name></name></author><category term="agiledeploymenttoolkit" /><summary type="html">Fully automated virgin server configuration and deployment with sensible default webserver and database configuration settings with best practice security guidelines baked in.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Agile Deployment Toolkit</title><link href="https://www.codebreakers.uk/agiledeploymenttoolkit/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Agile Deployment Toolkit" /><published>2021-11-01T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-11-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://www.codebreakers.uk/agile-deployment-toolkit</id><author><name></name></author><category term="agiledeploymenttoolkit" /><summary type="html">Toolkit Main Code Repositories</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Background Philosophy</title><link href="https://www.codebreakers.uk/backgroundphilosophy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Background Philosophy" /><published>2021-11-01T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-11-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://www.codebreakers.uk/adt-backgroundphilosophy</id><author><name></name></author><category term="agiledeploymenttoolkit" /><summary type="html">In “another life”, I was a consultant for a big IT outsourcing company used by the government for a lot of projects that they needed doing. The problem was the social disconnect. The users of the systems lived on a different planet to those of us building them. So, in order to be a “consultant with conviction”, I went to actually look, or, was led into looking by my intuitive self, to genuinely and deeply interact with the people that are end users of the systems as an end user of the systems so that I could actually advise based on experience rather than assumption. The old saying would be, “see if the chef will eat his own cooking” and that is what I essentially have been forced through and I noticed that my high paid consultant peers were very slow on the uptake to eat their own cooking and go through the same process of impoverishment which I have found is actually very enlightening. Its very very interesting psychologically the difference in the way that a person is perceived based on the position that they have massaged their way into in society. Do you have less to say when you are poor than when you are rich, actually you have more to say, so why is there a propensity to “listen to the rich man” and to “not listen to the poor man” its because in your idea of success the poor man can’t have much worth listening to otherwise he would be the rich man. Its beyond comprehension that there might actually be higher ideals and more worthwhile pursuits than simply making money and judging that as what it means to be a success. That’s vaccuous society myopia for you.</summary></entry></feed>